Finding Aid for Topographic Quadrangle Maps, 1895-[ongoing].
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 7.5 Minute, Scale 1:24,000
  - Loomis - Ozark SE
    - Ned Lake SE 46088C3
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Needmore 42084F7
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Negaunee 46087E5
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Negaunee NW 46087F6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Negaunee SW 46087E6
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Nestoria 46088E3
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Nettle Lake 41084F6 (Folder Nettle Lake-Northland NW)
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - New Baltimore 42082F6
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - New Buffalo East 41086G6
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - New Buffalo West 41086G7
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - New Greenleaf 43083F1
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - New Haven 42082F7
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - New Lothrop 43083A8
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Newaygo 43085D7
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Newberry 46085C5
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Niles East 41086G2
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Niles West 41086G3
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1973, green overprint
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - North Adams 41084H5
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1979; photorevised, green overprint
    - North Branch 43083B2
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - North Lake 45087D4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - North Point 45083A3
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Northland 46087A5
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Northland NE 46087B5
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1987, green overprint
    - Northland NW 46087B6
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Northville 42083D4 (Folder Northville-Ortonville)
      - Survey 1942; print 1945
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Northwest Albion 42084C7
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1980, green overprint
    - Norway 45087G8
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
    - Nottawa 41085H4
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1962, green overprint
    - Nunica 43086A1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Oak Grove 42083F8
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Oak Lake 44084G2
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Oak Ridge 46084C2
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Ocqueoc 45084D1
      - Survey 1982; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Ogemaw Springs 44084C3
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Ogontz 45086G7
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Olivet 42084D8
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1980, green overprint
    - Omer 44083A7
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Omer SW 44083A8
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Onaway 45084C2
      - Survey 1982; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Oregon 41083F4
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ortonville 42083G4
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Oscoda 44083D3 (Folder Oscoda-Ozark SE)
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Oskar 47088B6
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ossineke 44083H4
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Otisville 43083B5
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Otsego 42085D6
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Otsego Lake 44084H6
      - Survey 1950; print 1951
    - Otter Lake 46088H5
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Ovid East 43084A3
      - Survey 1974; print 1974; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - Owendale 43083F3
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Owosso North 43084A2
      - Survey 1974; print 1974; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - Owosso South 42084H2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Oxford 42083G3
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Ozark 46084B8
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ozark NE 46084B7
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Ozark SE 46084A7
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
  - Palmer- Shereman City
    - Palmer 46087D5 (Folder Palmer-Piatt Lake)
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Palms 43082E7
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Palmyra 41083G8
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Palo 43084A8
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Parkers Corners 42084E1
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Parma 42084C5
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Passage Island 48088B3
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Payment 46084E2
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Peacock 44085A8
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Peck 43082C7
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Pelkie 46088G6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Pendills Lake 46084D7
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Peninsula Point 45086F8
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Perch Lake 46088C6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Pere Cheney 44084E6
      - Survey 1950; print 1951
    - Perkins 45087H1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Perrinton 43084B6
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Perry 42084G2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Phelps 46089A1
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Phoenix 47088D3
      - Survey 1946; print 1947, green overprint
      - Survey 1946; print 1946; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1946; print 1946; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Piatt Lake 46085D1
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pickford 46084B3 (Folder Pickford-Point Lookout)
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pickford NW 46084B4
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pickford SE 46084A3
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pinckney 42083D8
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pinconning 43083G8
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pine Lake 46090C2
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Pine Lake 46088H6
      - Survey 1982; print 1984; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Pioneer 41084F5
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pittsford 41084G4
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1963, green overprint
    - Pleasant Lake 42084D3
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Pleasant Valley 43084E5
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Point Detour 45086E5
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Point Houghton 47088G8
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Point Isabelle 47087C8
      - Survey 1948; print 1949, green overprint
      - Survey 1948; print 1949; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Point Lookout 44083A5
      - Survey 1966; print 1966; reprint 1968, green overprint
      - Survey 1966; print 1966; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Point Mills 47088A4 (Folder Point Mills-Port Hope)
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1978; print 1978; reprint 1980; orthophotoquad
    - Point Patterson 45085H6
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Pointe Aux Chenes 45084H8
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Polaski 45083B6
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Pompeii 43084B5
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Pontchartrain Shores 46084A5
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pontiac North 42083F3
      - Survey 1941; print 1943
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Pontiac South 42083E3
      - Survey 1941; print 1943
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Poplar Lake 46086A7
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Port Austin East 44082A8
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1978; photorevised, green overprint
    - Port Austin West 44083A1
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Port Hope 43082H6
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Port Huron 42082H4 (Folder Port Huron-Quanicassee)
      - Survey 1937; print 1939
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1978; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1989; print 1991; reprint 1992; photorevised, green overprint
    - Port Sanilac 43082D5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Port Sheldon 42086H2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Portage 42085B5
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Portage Entry 46088H4
      - Survey 1982; print 1984; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Porter Lake 46088C5
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Portland North 42084H8
      - Survey 1975; print 1978; reprint 1979, green overprint
    - Portland South 42084G8
      - Survey 1975; print 1978; reprint 1979, green overprint
    - Posen 45083C6
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Powell Lake 46086C6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Prentiss Bay 45084H2
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Prescott 44083B8
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Presque Isle 45083C4
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Presque Isle, Wis. and Mich. 46089B6
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Price 42084H4
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Prickett Lake 46088F6
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Prudenville 44084C6
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Pullman 42086D1
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Quanicassee 43083E6
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Raco 46084C6 (Folder Raco-Redman)
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ralph 46087A7
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Ralph NE 46087B7
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ralph NW 46087B8
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ralph SW 46087A8
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Randville 45088H1
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
    - Rapid River 45086H8
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Rathbone 43084C4
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Rattle Run 42082G5
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Ravenna 43085B8
      - Survey 1975; print 1980; reprint 1980, green overprint
    - Reading 41084G6
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1977; photorevised, green overprint
    - Red Oak 44084F3
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Redford 42083D3
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Redman 43082H7
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Reed City North 43085H5 (Folder Reed City North-Rochester)
      - Survey 1982; print 1987; reprint 1987, green overprint
    - Reed City South 43085G5
      - Survey 1982; print 1987; reprint 1987, green overprint
    - Reese 43083D6
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Republic 46087D8
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Republic SW 46087C8
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Rexton 46085B2
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Rice Lake 47088B3
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Richmond 42082G7
      - Survey 1942; print 1945
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Richmondville 43082E5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Riley 42084H6
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - Riverdale 43084D7
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - Roberts Corner 46085C4
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Rochester 42083F2
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1981; photorevised, green overprint
    - Rock 46087A2 (Folder Rock-Roy Lake)
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Rock Harbor Lodge 48088B4
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Rock River 46086D8
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Rock SE 46087A1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Rockford 43085A5
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1972; photorevised, green overprint
    - Rockhouse Point 47088A8
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Rockwood 42083A2
      - Survey 1940; print 1942
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Rogers City 45083D7
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Rome Center 41084H2
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Romeo 42083G1
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Roscommon North 44084E5
      - Survey 1950; print 1951, green overprint
    - Roscommon South 44084D5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Rose City 44084D1
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - Roseburg 43082B6
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1976; photorevised
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1963, green overprint
    - Rosebush 43084F7
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976
    - Round Island 45084G5
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Roy Lake 46085D4
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Royal Oak 42083D2 (Folder Royal Oak-St. Helen NW)
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1981; photorevised, green overprint
    - Royston 45083B8
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Ruby 43082A5
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1963, green overprint
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Rudyard 46084B5
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Rush Lake 43083H2
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Rust 44083H8
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Ruth 43082F6
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Sage Lake 44083C8
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Saginaw 43083D8
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Saginaw NE 43083D7
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Sagola 46088A1
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
    - St. Charles 43084C2
      - Survey 1975; print 1975; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - St. Clair 42082G4
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1989; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - St. Clair Flats 42082E6
      - Survey 1937; print 1939
      - Survey 1937; print 1939; reprint 1949
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1978; photorevised, green overprint
    - St. Helen 44084C4
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - St. Helen NE 44084D3
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - St. Helen NW 44084D4
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - St. Ignace 45084G6 (Folder St. Ignace-Sanford)
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint